JIMMY GRANADINO

Los Angeles, CA | (323) 868-1802 | jimmy.granadino@gmail.com

Portfolio: http://jimmygranadino.com **Github:** http://github.com/jimmygranadino **LinkedIn:** http://linkedin.com/in/jimmygranadino

SUMMARY

I'm an enthusiastic solutions-driven developer with an eye towards implementations that optimize business functions. As an analyst by experience and a creative at heart pushing me forward, I deconstruct challenges to their base components to find efficient outcomes while utilizing my soft skills of bring teams together.

SKILLS

Skills: JavaScript, Python, SQL, HTML, CSS, jQuery, PostgreSQL, MongoDB, Express, Node.js, React.js, Next.js, Vue.js, RESTful APIs, CRUD Operations, Data Analysis, Financial Reporting, Project Management, Financial Modeling Languages: English, Spanish (professional proficiency)

EXPERIENCE

USC Credit Union | Los Angeles, CA

Nov. 2019 – May 2020

Real Estate Associate

- Shifted the Real Estate department from a paper loan file process by implementing a paperless software solution where I modeled a fully digital workflow during the COVID-19 crisis.
- Lead training of seasoned Real Estate personnel and re-assigned employees on loan packaging software capabilities and best practices under short notice with an immediate directive of becoming Work From Home capable.
- Aggregated data for reporting purposes related to various KPIs on a weekly, monthly and quarterly basis.

Blacksheep | Sydney, NSW

Music Performance Residency

Entertained patrons with carefully curated selection of music utilizing precise audio mixing and professional music production software while communicating safety needs to hospitality personnel on a weekly basis.

SmartBiz Loans | San Francisco, CA

Relationship Manager

Sep. 2016 – Jul. 2017

Dec. 2017 - Jul. 2018

- Managed a multimillion dollar portfolio of SBA 7(a) loans while working directly directly with business owners from dozens of industries throughout the United States and maintained a judicious relationship with senior lending partners to engage in prudent lending.
- Compiled and underwrote challenging SBA 7(a) loan packages in accordance with SBA Standard Operating Procedures and loan underwriting criteria as prescribed by partnered banks.
- Exceeded \$1.1MM monthly volume goal on multiple occasions while receiving company recognition.

Bay Federal Credit Union | Santa Cruz, CA

Jul. 2015 - Sep. 2016

Financial Analyst

- Launched and completed automation projects implemented organization-wide to eliminate hours of daily/weekly duties in various departments using SQL, VBA, and relevant programming languages or tools.
- Analyzed general ledger accounts, generated variance reporting, completed quarterly federal regulatory reports in partnership with Finance Manager, and produced monthly financial statements for board and senior leadership.
- Lead on reconciliation of multiple vendor platforms ensuring integrity of data, analytics and liquidity models.

EDUCATION

General Assembly Aug. 2020

Software Engineering Immersive

University of California, Santa Cruz

Dec. 2014

Bachelors in Economics; Minor in Technology & Information Management